{"data":[{"question":"I will call the police if you don't left me alone.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"will call","b":"if","c":"don't left","d":"alone","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Don't left-> don't leave","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"He lost his money simple because he wasn't careful.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"lost","b":"simple","c":"because","d":"careful","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Simple-> simply","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"We didn't hurry, so we miss the train.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"hurry","b":"so","c":"miss","d":"the train","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Miss-> missed","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"We are busy, so we won't join for you.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are busy","b":"so","c":"won't","d":"for","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- For-> with","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"If you had done as I told you, I think you would have succeeded now.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had done","b":"as","c":"think","d":"would have succeeded","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Would have succeeded -> would succeed","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"I am afraid I didn't have time to listen to you.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"am","b":"didn't","c":"to listen","d":"to you","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Didn't-> don't","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"I regret I didn't choose English since I started secondary school.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"regret","b":"choose","c":"since","d":"started","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Since-> when","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"The boy is too poor going to school.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The boy","b":"too poor","c":"going","d":"to","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Going-> to go","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Without Jack's help, I wouldn't have been able to moving the table.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Without","b":"Jack's help","c":"wouldn't have been","d":"moving","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Moving-> to move","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"I will phone you as soon as I arrived there.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"will phone","b":"as soon as","c":"arrived","d":"there","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Arrived-> arrive","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"}]}